>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 让我们试着澄清有关遗产的一些想法，好吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Let's try to clarify
some ideas around inheritance, okay?
因为我向你扔了很多东西
Because there is a lot of things
that I've thrown at you and
我只是想尽量把它做个直观的图表
I just wanna make as clear sort
of a visual diagram as I can.
在古典式的语言 C++， Java，之类的。
In classical oriented Languages C++,
Java, stuff like that.
当您创建类呼叫研讨会并将其实例化时，您在概念上
When you make a class call workshop and
you instantiate it, you are conceptually
在某些情况下，实际将其复制到这些实例中。
and in some cases, physically
copying down into those instances.
当你把一个儿童课称为另一个工作坊的时候
And when you make a child class call
another workshop that extends workshop,
你要把它复制到那个
you are copying down into that.
当您将该子类实例化时。
And when you instantiate that child class.
你在做更多的拷贝
You're doing more copies.
换句话说这些箭头从左到右从左到右
So in other words these arrows are going
from left to right, top to bottom,
因为它们本质上是复制操作
because they are fundamentally
copy operations.
当您尝试进行原型继承时，您有一个 workshop.prototype 对象。
When you try to do prototypal inheritance,
you have a workshop.prototype object.
然后再让另一个对象如 deepJS 或
And then you make another
object like deepJS or
reattJS，这些对象链接到 Workshop.prototype。
reactJS, those objects are linked
to Workshop.prototype.
然后，当您创建另一个workshop.原型时，它是链接到的。
And then when you make another
workshop.prototype it is linked to.
然后，当您制作 JSRecentParts 时，它也会链接。
And then when you make
JSRecentParts it is linked too.
这里，箭头从右到左，从底部到顶部。
So here, the arrows go from right to left,
and bottom to top.
因为这是一个链接，不是一个副本。
Because this is a linkage, not a copy.
跟我来
Follow me.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这通常被称为原型继承。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: This is often to
referred to as prototypal inheritance.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我有很深的，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I have a deep,
对调用此原型继承的想法的问题。
troubling issue with the idea of
calling this prototypal inheritance.
这就是我的问题
And here is what my issue is.
" 原型 " 一词甚至不代表任何必须的人。
The word prototypal doesn't even really
mean anything concrete to must people.
没人知道这意味着什么
Nobody even really knows what that means.
他们只是把它和这个奇怪的系统联系起来。
They just associate it
with this strange system.
但遗产继承的意义非常大，它承载着大量的行李。
But the word inheritance has a very strong
meaning, it carries lots of baggage.
大多数人的大脑都被编程来思考遗传
And most people's brains have been
programmed to think about inheritance,
就像复制关系一样
as having copy relationships.
我们做的就是把这个混淆不清的
So what we did was we took
this confusing-sounding
像原型一样把它贴在另一个词的前面
fancy word like prototypal,
stuck it in front of another word.
然后我们假装没事，完全改变它的意义。
And then we pretended as if that's okay,
to completely reverse the meaning of it.
就像我站在你面前一边有一个苹果
It's as if I stood up in front of you and
I had an apple in one hand, and
另一个是橘子
an orange in the other.
然后我说，不，不，那不是一个苹果。
And then I said, no, no,
no that's not an apple.
这只是个红橙
That's just a red orange.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 你会看着我，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: You'd look at me like,
你称它不改变它是什么
what you call it doesn't
change what it is.
是个苹果对吧
It's an apple, right?
你管这叫什么都不改
What you call this doesn't
change what it is.
它只会造成更多的混乱。
It only creates more confusion.
20 多年的 JavaScript 开发人员感到困惑
For 20 plus years JavaScript
developers have been confused
在 JavaScript 工作中不进行分类。
by why don't classes in JavaScript work.
他们用其他语言做的，没有人有胆量
The way they do in other languages, and
nobody seems to have had the courage
告诉他们，那是因为系统完全是完全不同的。
to tell them, it's because the systems
are completely fundamentally different.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 在某种意义上，我们一直在迎合情感上的情感
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: We've been, in a sense,
pandering to the emotional attachment
到类设计模式，并在其顶部添加额外的复杂性
to the class design pattern and
adding extra complexity on top of
针对语法制糖设计师的 JavaScript 。
JavaScript to suit
the syntactic sugar designers.
不只是拥抱已经存在的 JavaScript 。
Instead of just embracing
what JavaScript already is.
拥抱它的原型系统，拥抱这一动态。
Embracing its prototype system,
embracing the dynamic this nature.
我们一直试图把所有这些东西放在它上
We keep trying to put all these other
things on it so that it can be a class
系统， dang ，肯定是班，实际上不是上课。
system, dang it, it's definitely classes,
and in reality it's not classes.
我们只是想做个更好的
It's just we're trying to do a better and
更能把它打成像上课的样子
better job of duct taping
it to look like classes.